maximumfun.org 2019-12-31

# MaximumFun.org Privacy Policy | Maximum Fun

### SECTION 1 – WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT.

#### Information you provide to us.

When you make a contribution to Maximum Fun, or start a membership with us, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, email address, shows you listen to, and payment information. If you are eligible for a physical gift, we also collect your gift preferences and your shipping address.

When you use our [contact form](https://maximumfun.org/contact) to get in touch with us, you also provide us with your name and email address.

#### Information we collect automatically

When you visit our website, our servers automatically collect information about your browser type, referring site, the date and time of your visit, and your IP address.

#### Information collected through cookies

When you visit our website, we may send one or more “cookies” – small text files – to your computer. These include our own cookies and third-party cookies from services like Google Analytics. Some of these are essential to the functioning of this site. Others are used collect statistics on how visitors are using our site, including which pages they visit, how long they spend on individual pages, and how long they spend on the site as a whole. These statistics-linked cookies do not enable us to identify specific users of the site.

When you first visit our site, you are asked whether you want to opt into accepting statistics-linked cookies. You can also control or reset your acceptance of all cookies through your web browser. However, if you disable all cookies on the site, some site functionality may be limited.

### SECTION 2 – WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?

If you make a contribution to Maximum Fun, we store your name and email address to provide ongoing information regarding your account. We employ a third-party vendor, Recurly, to store your credit card information for ongoing payments under your membership (Recurly also processes these monthly payments, where applicable).

In addition, your email address is automatically added to the distribution list for our fundraising emails, which typically number fewer than 5 per year and come out in the months and weeks leading up to and during the MaxFunDrive.

If you use our contact form, your email address is used to respond to your inquiry, but for no other purpose.

If you opt-in, your email is also added to our monthly newsletter.

### SECTION 3 – CONSENT.

#### How do you get my consent?

When you provide us with personal information to make a donation, we conclude that you wish to become a member of Maximum Fun, and that you consent to our collecting your information and using it to fulfill payments and deliver membership gifts as appropriate. We also conclude that, by becoming a member, you consent to our use of your email address to update you on future MaxFun fundraising efforts.

#### How do I withdraw my consent?

If, after you sign up for membership and ongoing donations, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to withdraw monthly payments and/or to contact you, by the following means:

To stop your monthly payment, follow the link provided in your original donation confirmation email, or send an email to [donations@maximumfun.org](mailto:donations@maximumfun.org).  
To no longer receive fundraising notifications from us, use the “unsubscribe” link provided at the bottom of every periodic communication.

### SECTION 4 – DISCLOSURE.

We do not sell your personal information under any circumstances. We may pass certain information to third party vendors who help us to provide services to you (i.e., Recurly). We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

### SECTION 5 – RECURLY.

Monthly payments are processed by Recurly. They provide us with the online platform that allows us to manage monthly subscriptions, send out payment reminders, and process payments on a monthly basis.

Recurly stores your payment information in order to process monthly payments, and takes precautions to ensure the security of your Personal Data. However, they cannot guarantee that hackers / unauthorized personnel will not gain access to your Personal Data, despite their efforts.

### SECTION 5 – THIRD-PARTY SERVICES.

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway in the United States, then the personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service. This includes instances in which you initiate a third-party service from our site, as when you click a like / share button for a social media platform.

#### Links

When you click on links on our website, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

### SECTION 7 – SECURITY.

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS) provides a framework developing a robust security process for credit card transactions. Payments through Recurly are PCI-DSS Level 1 compliant.

### SECTION 8 – AGE OF CONSENT.

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

### SECTION 9 – CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our company is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to provide you with services.

### QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Managing Director at [bikram@maximumfun.org](mailto:bikram@maximumfun.org) or by mail at Maximum Fun, Inc.

Attn: Bikram Chatterji  
2404 Wilshire Blvd, Suite 9A, Los Angeles, CA, 90057, United States

Last revised: 10/24/2019
